Become my favorite Welcome back to the channel So
look who can say with our Jupiter with some juice it is a
little complete
so subscribe wife in the video I will
show you the youth subscribe
like and subscribe the channel let's
start the video friends see this
I did this this this this this fell down and
subscribe you will get to know
see this and behind also see
here there are strange marks also the
stone fell there it is not that
anything happened with much force but the vehicle fell that
means it fell slowly on Meena so see one
thing is already there see here by
keeping this stuff how have you
protected it by putting a trap so in this dress
code and look here below also
you will find some dirt
but there are scratches also on the waist now you are
more intelligent my subscriber so
come watch this and let me tell you after this
see if you keep it covered then you can subscribe by using this jugaad
but it gets removed after cleaning it the
scooty has fallen now so you must know how it gets so
this  See,
in this video I
can tell you a small answer about our scooter which I have given, so
see, if you also want to say something
about our beloved scooter then say
this, see, a little bit of wax is coming out of the seat cover, I do
n't know how it came out, but
as it did not hit much when the scooter fell, it is a
good thing, rest of the reassembled party scooter,
what is the scooter, the condition of the scooter is good but it is
good, see, is it not a good vehicle,
which Divya Sain has used in it and let me
tell you that this is the base model, you will find out by
looking at this line, it is
Bhim halogen light, so see,
today I have
told a little about it, so if you liked the video, then you should
like it, subscribe Baba Jai
Hind Jai Bharat Maa
Jhal